export const questions = [
  {
    question: "What is my middle name?",
    options: ["A: Warigia", "B: Wanjiku", "C: Wanjiru", "D: Wangari"],
    correct: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "What is my zodiac sign?",
    options: [
      "A: Taurus",
      "B: Cancer",
      "C: Capricorn",
      "D: Aries"
    ],
    correct: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "What is my mother's name?",
    options: ["A: Jane", "B: Mary", "C: Janet", "D: Miriam"],
    correct: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "How old was I when I had my first kiss??",
    options: ["A: 13", "B: 14", "C: 15", "D: 16"],
    correct: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "How old am I",
    options: ["A: 22", "B: 23", "C: 24", "D: 25"],
    correct: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "What is my favorite thing to do?",
    options: ["A: Have sex", "B: Eat", "C: Go to the club", "D: Sleep"],
    correct: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "What is my favorite color?",
    options: ["A: Black", "B: Blue", "C: Pink", "D: White"],
    correct: "D"
  },
  {
    question: "What is my favorite nail shape?",
    options: ["A: Coffin", "B: Stiletto", "C: Square", "D: Almond"],
    correct: "Square"
  },
  {
    question: "What is my favorite brand of soda?",
    options: ["A: Sprite", "B: Black Currant", "C: Fanta Orange", "D: Fanta Passion"],
    correct: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "How much do you love me?",
    options: ["A: 10", "B: 100", "C: 1000", "D: 10000"],
    correct:  "D"
  }
  ];